networking4all.com 2017-10-26

# Privacy Policy - Networking4all

## Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy for Networking4all B.V., located in Amsterdam and entered in the commercial register of the Chamber of Commerce under number 20099481 (hereinafter: "Networking4all"). This privacy policy describes the type of personal information we process and to what purpose. 

#### Use of personal information by Networking4all

Unless you are a customer with Networking4all, we only collect personal data when you visit our website by using cookies and visitor registration. When you are a customer with Networking4all, all information pertaining the collection of personal data and the purpose thereof can be found in the Terms and Conditions. 

#### The use of cookies and visitor registration

Cookies are small text files that are saved on the hard disk or in the memory of your computer. Networking4all uses cookies to improve the performance of our website. Cookies are not harmful to your computer. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can choose to do so in your browser. Some parts of our website may not function as intended without the use of cookies. Networking4all also registers the IP addresses of all visitors of our website, including the date and time of the visit. This information is saved for a maximum of 1 year and can for example be used to tally visitor numbers. 

#### Registered with Dutch DPA

Our procession of personal data has been registered with the [Dutch Data Protection Authority](https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/en). 

#### Updates privacy policy

This privacy policy may be subject to changes in the future. We strongly advise you to regularly read through this privacy policy. 

#### Contact

If you have any questions regarding the way in which Networking4all processes personal data, would like to review or edit your personal data, or would like to protest or receive further information regarding this privacy policy, you can contact Networking4all via [communication@networking4all.com](mailto:communication@networking4all.com).
